Let's take a view for Lombard for CGI,
Tapan, after the results, because the
company's profit has increased by 29%, the increase in net premium by
14% is especially showing us
how you will view this quarter.
I am quite positive in the overall insurance business here
because if you wait for these results, then okay, if it
comes out well, then there will be
no such issue in it and of course, it
will also increase going forward because if you look at their profit side, in
all respects, their premium side has
jumped by 44%, which is quite good. Let's
talk about retail health premium. Now again, if the
pressure came in the margins of those people
because their expansion had increased, but the
management has talked about that, it will also
bring the motor claim under control. In all of that, we
can say a little that the claim pass has increased, but I
think it is also hitting profitability,
but going forward  It will normalize. I
think that motor premium will
increase by 14-15% from here and at the end of the day
premium should also increase by almost 15%. So
if we look at it, it
seems that there can be a slight increase from here. Of course, these
people have got a little capital gain momentum.
Recently,
going forward in this quarter, the retail health segment is also
increasing significantly. If we talk about India's under-
penetration health insurance, then
these people will benefit from this and even
underwriting and the combine ratio are
also under control. So looking at all this, I
think that once these people
bring some efficiency in the expense ratio, then we will
get even better results from here. I
am positive that if anyone has this stock,
we can hold it.
I think that the insurance sector as a whole will have a
few years.  Will give decent returns. Even if it does
not out-perform, it can still give a decent return
.
Sir